A Guide to the Donald W. Gunter research material on Tommy Edwards, 1939-2018
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Donald W. Gunter research material on Tommy Edwards, 1939-2018
The Library of Virginia
52942
6.045 cubic feet and 14 boxes
Donald W. Gunter
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Donald W. Gunter of Richmond, Virginia.
Biographical Information
Thomas Jefferson Edwards was born 15 October 1922 in Henrico County, Virginia, to thomas Jefferson Edwards and Buena Vista Edwards. Tommy Edwards attended the Virginia Randolph Training School in Henrico County. At age 17 Edwards had a radio show on WRNL, Richmond, Virginia, singing songs and playing the piano. By 1943, he moved to New York, New York, and became a songwriter. In 1947, Edwards formed the Tommy Edwards Trio, releasing several songs. By 1950, he resumed his solo career, having moderate success. By 1958, his career seemed to have ended, when he re-released his 1951 hit "It's All in the Game." The song spent six weeks at the top of the Billboard charts. Edwards' career soon declined again. Edwards died in Henrico County 23 October 1969, and is buried in the Quioccasin Baptist Church Cemetery.
Scope and Content
Research material, 1939-2018, on Tommy Edwards (1922-1969) of Henrico County, Virginia, collected by Donald W. Gunter in preparation of a biography for the Dictionary of Virginia Biography. Collection includes biographical information on Edwards' life and career as a songwriter and singer; chart information on songs that Edwards wrote or sung; information on and recordings of Edwards' albums and records; power points and related materials for talks and interviews on Edwards by Donald W. Gunter; subject files containing background information relating to Edwards; and records and materials used in an exhibit on Edwards at a celebration of Henrico County's 400th anniversary.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged
Series I: Biographical Information
Series II: Charts
Series III: Discography
Series IV: Don Gunter Correspondence and Presentations
Series V: General Subjects
Seres VI: Henrico County 400th Anniversary
Contents List
- Series I: Biographical information., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
  Series I: Biographical information contains articles, biographical sketches, documentaries, family genealogies and records, interviews, obituaries, proclamations, and other papers detailing Tommy Edwards' life, career, and death. Also details renewed interest in Edwards, including the establishment of a historic marker near his childhood home and a Tommy Edwards Day proclamation.
  - Taken by the Music: The Tommy Edwards Story by Don Gunter (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tommy Edwards biographies from the Dictionary of Virginia Biography and Encyclopedia Virginia (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tommy Edwards: Henrico's Hit Maker (Henrico County) and Remembering Richmond's Tommy Edwards (WCVE-23) documentaries (DVD) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tommy Edwards biographical sketch from The Encyclopedia of Popular Music (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Edwards family history and records (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - World War II draft registration records (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - WRNL radio show listings, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Caravan of Stars clippings, May 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Edwards family obituaries, 1958, 1969, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - All in the Game: The Rise and Fall of a Richmond Crooner, Richmond.com, 3 November 2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Tommy Edwards' posthumus royalties, May 2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Richmond Times-Dispatch articles on Tommy Edwards historical marker and documentary, 1 January 2008, 25 June 2009, 4, 11, and 20 January 2018 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Henrico Citizen articles on Tommy Edwards and on historical marker, 20 March-2 April 2008, 18 June-1 July 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Tommy Edwards historical marker--Department of Historic Resources, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tommy Edwards Day Proclamation--Richmond, 15 October 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Tommy Edwards outline (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Tommy Edwards timeline (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Harriet Edwards interviews, 28 September 2007, 14 March 2008, 20 February 2009 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Post-marker interviews at Quioccasin Baptist Church, 26 September 2007 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Edwards family search (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - African Americans to be honored by Henrico County (including Tommy Edwards) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Tommy Edwards image (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Series II: Charts, 1943-2004., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
  Series II: Charts contains information from various publications such as Billboard, Variety, Cash Box, Down Beat and Metronome showing where Tommy Edwards' records charted.
  - Billboard, 1943-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Billboard orders (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Variety, 1951-1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Variety charts, revised 6 January 2008 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cash Box, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cash Box, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Down Beat, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Metronome, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Joel Whitburn's Pop Hits compilations--Tommy Edwards references (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tommy Edwards--songs on charts (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous charts--Tommy Edwards (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Series III: Discography., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 2-3)
  Series III: Discography contains information on the records and albums recorded by Tommy Edwards, as well as information on songs written by Edwards and sung by other performers. Includes cds, discographies, videos, images of album covers, and related materials.
  - Tommy Edwards: The Singles Collection, 1949-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - CDs of albums and recordings (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tommy Edwards playlists: MGM singles, various recordings, and various MGM album tracts, 1951-1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Video clips of Tommy Edwards on the Ed Sullivan Show and Dick Clark Saturday Night Beechnut Show (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Tommy Edwards discography (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Tommy Edwards discography, revised 14 November 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Online biographies/discographies of Tommy Edwards (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Hit records, 1950-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Tommy Edwards discography--Mike Callahan compilation (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Tommy Edwards discography--William Tharp compilation (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Albums (cover images) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Albums (cover images) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Records (images) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The MGM Labels: A Discography, volume I, 1946-1960 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The MGM Labels: A Discography, volume II, 1960-1982 and volume III: additional recordings/record and artist indexes (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - MGM Album Discography sections from parts 1, 5, 6, 7, 14, 19, and Lion Album Discography (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The MGM Records Story (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Album notes for Tommy Edwards: It's all in the Game The MGM Recordings, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Album notes (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - It's all in the Game" discography information (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - My Bicycle Tillie by Tommy Edwards (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Copyright information (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - First search catalog search on Tommy Edwards records and albums (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--all returns on search (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--It's all in the Game (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--albums (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--78s (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--45s (A-H) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--45s (I) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Recordings identified on eBay--45s (M-V, various) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sheet music identified on eBay (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Recordings identified at online sellers (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Don Gunter Correspondence and Presentations., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 3-4)
  Series IV: Don Gunter Correspondence and Presentations contains advertisements, agendas, articles, email correspondence, interviews, lists, notes, photographs, power point presentations, and related papers for interviews, presentations, and talks delivered by Don Gunter on Tommy Edwards. Email correspondence also covers Gunter's research on Edwards.
  - Don Gunter correspondence, A-C (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Mike Callahan--BSN Publications (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Katherine Calos (with Ed Critzer, Glenn Crone, Wade Crump, Guillermo Gray, Andrew Ryan, and Jim Scott) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, D-I (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, L-P (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Hank Moore (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Bill Shurk--Bowling Green State University (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, S-T (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, W (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Paul Wheatley (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Janet Wheeler (Harriet Edwards) (with Lloyd Peace) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Don Gunter correspondence, Tommy Edwards Day (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Don Gunter presentation on Tommy Edwards at the Library of Virginia, 19 February 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Don Gunter presentation on Tommy Edwards at the Library of Virginia--photographs, 19 February 2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Don Gunter presentation on Tommy Edwards at Tuckahoe Library (Henrico County), 18 October 2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Power point presentations on Tommy Edwards, including audio clips (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Don Gunter presentation on Tommy Edwards at Glen Allen Library (Henrico County), 21 April 2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Tommy Edwards power point images--hard copies (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Tommy Edwards power point images--hard copies (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Power point song list (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Conversion (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - List of power point presentations and media interviews (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - PBS Tommy Edwards Documentary interview, 10 July 2017 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Henrico County Documentary--Tommy Edwards questions (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - University of Richmond Rock and Roll Seminar--power point notes (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Henrico 2011 African American Subcommittee meeting agenda, 22 February 2010 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Library of Virginia Broadside magazine, Summer 2008, Fall 2009, Fall 202 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Review, July/August 2008 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hunt for Henrico History 2011 Exhibitor Application, 11 January 2011 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Tommy Edwards notes (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Google Books search on Tommy Edwards (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Series V: General Subjects., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 4-5)
  Series V: General Subjects includes materials gathered by Don Gunter concerning singers, song writers, records, recording studios, locations, and other information to provide context and background for his research on Tommy Edwards.
  - Louis Armstrong (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Tony Bennett (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bobby Blue Bland (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Martin Block (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ruth Brown (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Ray Charles--Modern Sounds in Country and Western Music, Volume 2 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Dick Clark (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Rosemary Clooney (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Nat King Cole (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sam Cook (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Charles G. Dawes (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Tommy Dorsey (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Pete Drake (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Billy Eckstine (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Red Foley (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Tony Fontane (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Fredric Fradkin (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Connie Francis (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Alan Freed (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Cecil Gant (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Dale Hawkins (and Tommy Edwards) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Belford Hendricks (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Jimmy Hilliard (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Leroy Holmes (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Keith Jarrett (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Norman Jewison--Lucky Strike, Your Hit Parade, and Tommy Edwards (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Louis Jordan (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Sammy Kaye (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fritz Kreisler (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Robert Q. Lewis (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Barry Manilow (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Adam Clayton Powell (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Elvis Presley (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sammy Price (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Teddy Randazzo (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Randolph (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Johnnie Ray (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Herman Roberts (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Cliff Richard (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chris Rouse--Rubin Mitchell Trio (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dinah Shore (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Carl Sigman (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bill Silbert (including information on letters to him, including from Tommy Edwards) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tommy Smalls--Dr. Jive (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Eddie South (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Billy Tolles (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Andy Williams (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hank Williams biograph--references to Tommy Edwards (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Earl Wilson (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Si Zentner (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bill Samuels--Cats 'n' Jammer Three (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Deep River Boys (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Four Tops (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Lambert, Hendricks, and Ross (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Prisonaires (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Record Makers and Breakers: Voices of the Independent Rock 'n' Roll Pioneers (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - It's All in the Game (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - I Really Don't Want to Know (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - I Wish You Love (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Rock and Roll Music (Chuck Berry) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Secret Love (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - That's All (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Songs for Sale (TV show) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - About Face (movie) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Brill Building (New York) (see also Tin Pan Alley) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Fack's in San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Howard Theatre (Washington D.C.) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Kitten's Korner (Atlanta) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Parsons the New School for Design (New York) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - The Round Table (Henrico County) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Tin Pan Alley (New York) (see also Brill Building) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Tivoli Theater (Chicago) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School (Hanover County) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - YMCA (Harlem) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Pittsburgh night spots (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Billboard Hot 100 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Chitlin' Circuit (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Cross Canada Hit Parade (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Henrico Citizen--award for Tommy Edwards story (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Record labels--Musicor, National, Regent, Savoy, Signature (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Show Business Business from Life, 22 December 1958 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - A & R (artists and repertoire) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Crooners (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Music of the post-war era (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Novelty song (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Rock and Roll (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - First search--library searches (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Series VI: Henrico County 400th Anniversary, 2011., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 6-7)
  Series VI: Henrico County 400th Anniversary contains exhibition materials gathered by Don Gunter to highlight Henrico native Tommy Edwards' musical career. Exhibit materials include records, posters, and signage. Also includes a DVD titled Henrico's Legacy: Commemorating 400 Years.
  - Sweet Emalina, My Gal/Huckleberry Heaven (Tommy Edwards Trio) (78) (Box 6)
  - Up in the Alley/A Long Time (Tommy Edwards Trio) (78) (Box 6)
  - Once There Lived a Fool/A Friend of Johnny's (78), 1950 (Box 6)
  - Once There Lived a Fool/A Friend of Johnny's (78), 1950 (Box 6)
  - It's All in the Game/All Over Again (78), 1951 (Box 6)
  - A Fool Such as I/I Can't Love Another (78), 1952 (Box 6)
  - A Fool Such as I/I Can't Love Another (78), 1952 (Box 6)
  - You Win Again/Sinner or Saint (78), 1952 (Box 6)
  - It's All in the Game/Please Love Me Forever (45), 1958 (Box 6)
  - Please Mr. Sun/The Morningside of the Mountain (45) (Box 6)
  - Exhibition papers relating to Tommy Edwards (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition posters and signage relating to Tommy Edwards (Box 7)
  - Henrico's Legacy: Commemorating 400 Years (Box 7)
- Oversize materials., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 8-11)
  Contains oversize materials from Series I: Biographical Information; Series II: Charts; and Series IV: Don Gunter Correspondence and Presentations.
  - Richmond Times-Dispatch articles, 1 January 2008, 25 June 2009, 4 and 11 January 2018 (from Series I: box 1, folder 20) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Henrico Citizen articles, 20 March-2 April 2008, 18 June-1 July 2009 (from Series I: box 1, folder 21) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Site/location plan for Tommy Edwards historical marker (from Series I: box 1, folder 22) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1943-1945 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1946 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1947 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1948 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1949 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1950 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, January-August 1951 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, September-December 1951 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, January-May 1952 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, July-December 1952 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, January-April 1953 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, May-December 1953 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1954 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1955 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1956-1957 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, July-October 1958 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, November-December 1958 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, January-April 1959 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, May-December 1959 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, January-June 1960 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, July-December 1960 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Billboard articles and mentions, 1961-1968, 2002, 2004 (from Series II: box 2, folder 1) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Variety articles and mentions, 1951 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Variety articles and mentions, 1952 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Variety articles and mentions, January-June 1953 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Variety articles and mentions, August-November 1953 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Variety articles and mentions, 1954 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Variety articles and mentions, 1958 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Variety articles and mentions, 1959 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Variety articles and mentions, 1960-1962 (from Series II: box 2, folder 3) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Don Gunter presentation on Tommy Edwards at the Library of Virginia--photographic proofs, 19 February 2008 (from Series IV: box 4, folder 2) (Box 11, Folder 9)
- CDs., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 12-13)
  Contains CDs from Series I: Biographical Information; Series III: Discography; and Series IV: Don Gunter Correspondence and Presentations.
  - Remembering Richmond's Tommy Edwards (from Series I: box 1, folder 3) (Box 12)
  - Tommy Edwards (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - Tommy Edwards: It's All in the Game (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - Tommy Edwards: The Lamp Is Low (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - The Very Best of Tommy Edwards (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - Tommy Edwards: Greatest Hits (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - Songs written or sung by Tommy Edwards, including other performers (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - It's All in the Game by other singers (from Series III: box 2, folder 13) (Box 12)
  - MGM Singles, 1951-1955 (from Series III: box 2, folder 14) (Box 12)
  - MGM various recordings, 1951-1965 (from Series III: box 2, folder 14) (Box 12)
  - Various MGM album tracks (from Series III: box 2, folder 14) (Box 12)
  - Ed Sullivan Show, 14 September and 9 November 1958 (from Series III: box 2, folder 15) (copy 1) (Box 12)
  - Ed Sullivan Show, 14 September and 9 November 1958 (from Series III: box 2, folder 15) (copy 2) (Box 12)
  - Dick Clark Beechnut Show, 14 March, 8 August, 12 September 1959, 12 February 1960 (from Series III: box 2, folder 15) (Box 12)
  - Power points created by Don Gunter, including sound files. Also includes photographs from LVA talk and flash drive (from Series IV: box 4, folders 4-5) (Box 13)
- Oversize materials., Extent: 1 box. (Box 14)
  Contains oversize materials from Series I: Biographical Information and Series IV: Don Gunter Correspondence and Presentations.
  - Richmond Times-Dispatch article Voice of the Past, poster and printed copy (from Series I: box 1, folder 20) (Box 14)
  - Poster for Dictionary of Virginia Biogaphy volume 4--Tommy Edwards (from Series IV: box 4, folder 1) (Box 14)
  - Poster for Don Gunter's presentation on Tommy Edwards at the Library of Virginia, 19 February 2008 (from Series IV: box 4, folder 1) (Box 14)
  - Poster for Don Gunter's presentation on Tommy Edwards at the Glen Allen Library (Henrico County), 21 April 2011 (from Series IV: box 4, folder 5) (Box 14)
  - Poster of Broadside cover, Summer 2008 (from Series IV: box 4, folder 15) (Box 14)